file:///storage/emulated/0/PerMaryRoseAnne2C_HTMLCSS/Image/Yeng.jpg

• Home
• History
• Artist
• Contact
• About us

file:///storage/emulated/0/PerMaryRoseAnne2C_HTMLCSS/Image/Yeng8.jpg

MENU

•Yeng Constantino 
•Song 
•Album 
•Popularity 

HOME

Yeng Constantino “Pop-Rock Superstar” Yeng Constantino’s talent for writing songs and making music that is not only relatable but also full of heart is what makes her an OPM favorite. Having released songs like “Hawak Kamay,” “Salamat,” “Cool Off,” “Chinito,” and “Ikaw,” fans will always sing along to this multi-awarded artist’s masterpieces. Yeng Constantino was just 17 when "Hawak-Kamay," the song she composed and performed in the first week of Pinoy Dream Academy in 2006, became an airwave sensation."Ikaw" also gave Yeng the Song of the Year trophies from the 2015 PMPC Star Awards for Music and the 2015 Awit Awards.

SONGS 

Ikaw 
Ako muna
 Salamat 
Tahimik 
Cool off 
Paasa 
Hawak kamay 
Jeepney love story
 Lapit 
Babay 
Chinito 
If we fall in love
Siguro 
Pag ayaw muna 
Kulang 
Dasal 
Haligi 
Habambuhay 
Unat huling pag ibig 
Pag ibig 
Kapag ako ay nag mahal 
Dance without the music 
Feels like

POPULARITY

Yeng Constantino is already an icon in the Philippine music industry. The amazing thing is, she's good at acting as well and has an award from the Metro Manila Film Festival 2019 to show for it.In 2009, she released "Lapit," another inspirational rock song, and "Jeepney Love Story," a romantic song that received a lot of attention owing to its cute music video that featured a cameo of Piolo Pascual.Yeng released another massive hit in 2013. The song was "Chinito," a charming ditty that she claimed was dedicated to Enchong Dee.The song's video featuring the Kapamilya actor was her most-viewed music video at that time. Enchong was so enthralled with the song that he officially released his own single of "Chinito."In August 2014, Yeng released "Ikaw," a romantic ballad she composed as a prelude to her wedding with her then fiancé, Victor Christian "Yan" Asuncion. Yeng has made an impressive mark in the showbiz industry with 14 years in music.She’s a respected icon who is dubbed the Pop Rock Princess. She has judged several singing competitions, including Tawag ng Tanghalan, Pinoy Boyband Superstar and We Love OPM.Yeng has over 292 million career streams on Spotify, becoming one of the Most Streamed Filipino artists of all time and has over 32 million accumulated views on her official YouTube channel with over a million subscribers as well. Her timeless hit Ikaw is also listed as the second most viewed OPM music video by a Female Filipino solo artist and 6th overall as of May 2021. 

©2022 Yengster Bacong bacong, Gasan, Marinduque- Philippines 
Tel No. 0945-649-8665. All rights reserved